i think i'm officially an american
because i make fun of walmart now
i don't even go there i don't look down
at walmart
that's a very american thing you
understand like this country's so
luxurious people make fun
of walmart
growing up in yemen our local store was
a metallic box the size of a kitchen
like the first time i saw walmart
honestly it was more exciting than the
day i met my nephew
i walked in and i saw a mcdonald's in
there and it blew my mind i was like
there's a mcdonald's in the store
there's not one mcdonald in the whole
country of yemen
like that made me believe in the
american dream
and i remember being that easily
impressed i remember being that way and
now what i do is if somebody moves here
from yemen for the first time i mess
with them
my cousin came here for the first time
and i took him to white castle and i
convinced him that white castle was a
five star restaurant
i was like this place was founded by
george washington himself
it used to be called a castle of whites
i didn't even let him go in i said you
need the special membership to get in
wait outside
i went in i got some food and i caught
my cousin taking selfies
at a parking lot of white castle like he
was living a high life
and he looked at me and said
i'm in arabic that means this is the
most beautiful day
and i was like ahmed
we haven't even been to walmart yet
pace yourself is going to be a big deal
[Applause]
fun story i was once arrested
because the cops thought it was the
mexican guy they were looking for
which was weird because at the time i
was not mexican
that was a quick phase in college
uh here's what happened i didn't know
this but a couple i never met got into
an argument it was a latino couple and
the husband was not a nice guy he hit
his wife in the face
and the daughter saw this and she called
the cops on her father and then he took
off on his bicycle like a villain on
welfare
and at that exact moment i was not on a
bicycle i was just walking just being
all mexican
and the cops saw me and they're like yep
close enough
and they took my id they arrested me
they put me in the back of the car and
they drove three blocks and dropped me
off to this very confused looking mother
and she looked at me and she said who is
this guy
and i said don't talk to your husband
that way poppy
and then i looked at the cop and i'm
like dude he should be like the best at
investigating you saw my id i have an
arabic name my name is ali sultan
not alejandro
and then the daughter came on she's like
that's not my dad
and i was like i actually am your father
now it's the law
there's gonna be some changes around
this house
rule number one snitches get stitches
[Music]
this
you